// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Jane turned 16 in', 
      a: 'Germany', 
      b: 'Switzerland',
      c: 'Greece',
      d: 'Italy',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Jane\'s  family owned how many chickens?', 
      a: '500', 
      b: '5000',
      c: '10000',
      d: '15000',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'To what NFL coach did Jane say "Brett Favre is my man" (though she hates him now)?', 
      a: 'Mike Shanahan', 
      b: 'Jimmy Johnson',
      c: 'Roger Staubach',
      d: 'Mike Ditka',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Jane always wears a necklace with what on it?', 
      a: 'Cat', 
      b: 'Frog',
      c: 'Lizard',
      d: 'Turtle',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In whose memory does she wear that necklace?', 
      a: 'Her niece', 
      b: 'Her sister',
      c: 'Her mother',
      d: 'Her aunt',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many books did Jane read in first grade?', 
      a: '10', 
      b: '60',
      c: '110',
      d: '130',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'In high school, what sport did Jane letter in?', 
      a: 'Basketball', 
      b: 'Gymnastics',
      c: 'Track',
      d: 'Volleyball',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What did Jane see a shoplifter stuff in his pants?', 
      a: 'A frozen burrito', 
      b: 'A pack of hot dog buns',
      c: 'a frozen pizza',
      d: 'Two candy bars',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many days of school did Jane miss from 4th grade through junior year of high school?', 
      a: '0', 
      b: '5',
      c: '9',
      d: '18',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which celebrity did Jane enjoy meeting most?', 
      a: 'Dennis Quaid', 
      b: 'Zac Efron',
      c: 'Lea Thompson',
      d: 'Stephen Root',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};